<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Brave the Future</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_events">Events</string>
    <string name="title_activity_students">Students</string>


    <string name="event0">Hackathon</string>
    <string name="event1">Swag Design Challenge</string>
    <string name="event2">Candle Design Challenge</string>

    <string name="student0">Tino Kamungeremu</string>
    <string name="student1">Kizito Okoye</string>
    <string name="student2">Josh Arcilla</string>

    <string name="eventdesc0">\tWinning Team Will Receive $5,000!\n\n\tThe winning team may also have an opportunity to earn an additional $5,000 after the hackathon—see full contest rules for details.\n\n\tDate: Friday, February 8 at 4 p.m. - Sunday, February 10 at 4 p.m.\nLocation: SIRC 2020B\n\n\tThe race is on to develop an exciting and interactive app for our university\'s fundraising campaign—Brave The Future.\n\n\tTake part in a 48-hour hackathon to develop an app prototype that will engage users to explore Brave The Future.\n\n\tAs part of the hackathon, you will present your app prototype in a live five-minute pitch to a panel of judges. The final app should be a mobile app for iOS and/or Android.\n\n\tThe winning app will become an interactive component of the Brave The Future campaign.\n\n\tFood will be provided to registered participants throughout the event.\n\n\tPlease read the hackathon rules and guidelines carefully before registering.</string>
    <string name="eventdesc1">\tWork individually or as a team to develop the concept for an exciting and unique promotional give-away that reflects the bold, optimistic perspective of Brave The Future. Be inspired by new technology and create an innovative item that is unique to the university.\n\n\tAs part of the competition, you may be selected to present your design concept in a live three-minute entrepreneurial pitch to a panel of judges.\n\n\tThe winning design concept may be developed and manufactured into a Brave The Future branded product and used as a promotional item throughout the campaign.</string>
    <string name="eventdesc2">\tWork individually or as a team to design an innovative candle mould that reflects the bold, optimistic perspective of the Brave The Future campaign. Be inspired and help support the university\'s sustainability initiatives by designing a candle mould that transforms beeswax harvested from the Pollinator Project into stylish and \'brave\' candles!\n\n\tThe university\'s Pollinator Project encompasses 31 bee hives, a pollinator garden, community gardens, bat homes and a greenhouse, to promote and support pollinators in our environment. The winning candle design will be sold on campus as a Brave The Future campaign branded promotional item with proceeds used to support the operation and growth of the Pollinator Project.\n\n\tThe Candle Design Challenge is now closed. Thank you to all students who submitted an entry to the competition.</string>

    <string name="student_story0">\tTino Kamungeremu has an insatiable ambition. When the second-year Mechatronics student was accepted into his program at the University of Ontario Institute of Technology he had one all-consuming goal in mind: to be at the forefront of the autonomous vehicle movement. I want to contribute to the development of technology that has positive effects on society,” he says.\n\n\tWhen Tino arrived on campus, he was immediately impressed by the wide range of classes, professors’ commitment to their students and how smart his fellow students proved to be. He felt at home and ready for anything.\n\n\t“I was attracted by the friendly, supportive atmosphere and the tech-enriched facilities and learning environment,” he says.\n\n\tTino’s fascination with robots began at a young age and continued through high school, where he took a keen interest in math and science. He dreams of one day working for Google who is racing to develop fully autonomous vehicles to meet the demands of an increasingly connected and fast-paced world.\n\n\tAs the eldest child of a single parent family and a first generation immigrant, Tino was further motivated to achieve his educational goals when he received the Lenovo Canada Inc. Access bursary in 2018.  “When I received this award, it gave me a sense of inspiration knowing there are people out there that are supporting me.”\n\n\tWhen he’s not attending lectures or working in the lab, Tino can be found playing intermural sports and hopes to make the university basketball team.</string>
    <string name="student_story1">\tTino Kamungeremu has an insatiable ambition. When the second-year Mechatronics student was accepted into his program at the University of Ontario Institute of Technology he had one all-consuming goal in mind: to be at the forefront of the autonomous vehicle movement. I want to contribute to the development of technology that has positive effects on society,” he says.\n\n\tWhen Tino arrived on campus, he was immediately impressed by the wide range of classes, professors’ commitment to their students and how smart his fellow students proved to be. He felt at home and ready for anything.\n\n\t“I was attracted by the friendly, supportive atmosphere and the tech-enriched facilities and learning environment,” he says.</string>
    <string name="student_story2">\tTino Kamungeremu has an insatiable ambition. When the second-year Mechatronics student was accepted into his program at the University of Ontario Institute of Technology he had one all-consuming goal in mind: to be at the forefront of the autonomous vehicle movement. I want to contribute to the development of technology that has positive effects on society,” he says.\n\n\tWhen Tino arrived on campus, he was immediately impressed by the wide range of classes, professors’ commitment to their students and how smart his fellow students proved to be. He felt at home and ready for anything.\n\n\t\n\n\t“I was attracted by the friendly, supportive atmosphere and the tech-enriched facilities and learning environment,” he says.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_places">Places</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_talents">Talents</string>

    <string name="prof0">Dr. Chris Collins</string>
    <string name="prof1">Dr. Rupinder Brar</string>
    <string name="prof2">Dr. Steven Murphy</string>

    <string name="prof_story0">\t\tI am an associate professor and Canada Research Chair in Linguistic Information Visualization at the University of Ontario Institute of Technology (UOIT), where I lead a lab of 10 students at various levels of study. My research focus is interdisciplinary, combining information visualization and human-computer interaction with natural language processing to address the challenges of linguistic information management and the problems of information overload.\n\n\t - Dr. Chris Collins</string>
    <string name="prof_story1">\t\tThe University of Ontario Institute of Technology (UOIT) is celebrating along with Dr. Rupinder Brar, a Physics lecturer with the Faculty of Science, for having won TVO\'s 2010 Big Ideas Best Lecturer Competition. This marks the second time in the five-year history of the competition that a UOIT lecturer has won top prize.\n\n\t"I am sincerely honoured to have been selected as Ontario\'s Best Lecturer," said Dr. Brar. "Teaching is my passion and I thoroughly enjoy challenging and inspiring my students to push their own boundaries of thinking and learning. I would like to thank my students for the nomination and the amazing support I have received from them and the UOIT community.\n\n\tDr. Brar was announced as the winner during the airing of TVO\'s Big Ideas television show on Saturday, following a competition that began last fall with a call for nominees from Ontario\'s universities and colleges. He was nominated by one of his students.\n\n\tDr. Brar\'s winning lecture was titled Exoplanets: The Search for Other Earths, and for being named Ontario\'s top lecturer, a $10,000 TD Meloche Monnex scholarship will be awarded to UOIT.\n\n\tA total of 692 professors were originally nominated and of those 332 accepted the nomination. A panel of judges narrowed the impressive list down to 20, followed by the Top 10 shortlist comprised of five men and five women whose televised lectures aired on TVO\'s Big Ideas in March and April. Dr. Brar was selected as the winner after the close of the voting period on April 11 and announced during the show on Saturday, April 17.\n\n\t"Congratulations to Dr. Brar for this well-deserved recognition," said Dr. William Smith, dean, Faculty of Science. "He is a shining example of the caliber of our world-class professors at UOIT who are dedicated to enhancing their students\' knowledge and understanding in their chosen fields. Dr. Brar\'s enthusiasm for teaching and his ability to engage and inspire students in new areas of science and to comprehend complex Physics subject matter is underscored with this win."\n\n\tDr. Brar joined UOIT as Physics lecturer when the university opened its doors in 2003. He earned his Bachelor of Science (Honours) in Physics, Astronomy and Mathematical Science degree from the University of Toronto and went on to complete his Master of Science in Physics and Astronomy degree from the University of Waterloo and his PhD in Physics from Queen\'s University. While at Queen\'s he was awarded the Christopher Knapper Award for Excellence in Teaching Assistance. During graduate school, Dr. Brar researched the halos of spiral galaxies while at the same time he discovered his love for teaching Physics and Astronomy to undergraduate students. Brar has received numerous awards and accolades for his teaching. He has a reputation for effectively communicating complex topics in physics and astronomy to undergraduate students of varying backgrounds with a lecturing style that is engaging, entertaining and interactive.\n\n\tWhen he is not teaching, Dr. Brar conducts astrophysics research and is actively involved in a wide range of cultural, environmental and political groups.</string>
    <string name="prof_story2">\t\tThe University of Ontario Institute of Technology has ambitious plans to create a better Canada and a better world. I am pleased that those plans are rooted in a commitment to social, scientific and economic innovations as well as in equity, diversity and inclusivity. I am dedicated to making our university a globally recognized change-maker and a leader in technology-driven research and scholarship.”\n\n\t\t - Steven Murphy, PhD, incoming President and Vice-Chancellor, University of Ontario Institute of Technology</string>
    <string name="title_activity_research">Research</string>

    <string name="research0">Big Data</string>
    <string name="research1">Brilliant Entrepreneurs</string>
    <string name="research2">Moving Ground Plane</string>

    <string name="researchdesc0">\tAs one of Canada\'s newest research-intensive universities, the University of Ontario Institute of Technology (UOIT) has emerged as a key leader in the area of Big Data streaming analytics and visualization—and its application into various domains.\n\n\t\tThe university\'s research development in information and communications technology, and informatics brings together core expertise (computer scientists, biomedical engineers and social scientists), and leading industrial partners, such as SickKids and IBM, to offer transformational leadership in the evolving digital age.\n\n\t\tThe university also has ties with the Region of Durham\'s growing entrepreneurial network that accelerates the movement of discovery to market.</string>
    <string name="researchdesc1">\tCanada needs entrepreneurs, and in today\'s competitive job market, students require entrepreneurial skills, whether in business for themselves, as agents of social change, or as innovative employees within organizations. Brilliant Entrepreneurship supports student, recent alumni and faculty success while building an entrepreneurial culture on campus.\n\n\t\tThinking about starting a business? Just have an idea? Looking to join a startup team? Curious about entrepreneurship? If you answer yes to one or more of these questions, Brilliant Entrepreneurship is for you!</string>
    <string name="researchdesc2">\tThe Province of Ontario, Magna International Incorporated and Multimatic Incorporated are partnering with the University of Ontario Institute of Technology to revolutionize the university’s ACE research facility, making it the most comprehensive aerodynamic and thermal test centre in the world.\n\n\t\tThrough the partnership, ACE will enhance its one-of-a-kind research facility by adding a Moving Ground Plane—a giant belt that acts as a road moving under a vehicle, simulating the aerodynamic forces against moving vehicles, and measuring physical characteristics in real-world conditions.</string>

</resources>
